bodycandy.com 2015-04-29

# Body Candy Body Jewelry

> Privacy Policy Statement for bodycandy.com
> 
> **Information Collection and Use:**
> 
> Cybercartel International, Inc. (BodyCandy.com) is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to any third party and we will only share this information in the processing of your order. 
> 
> **Sharing:**
> 
> We use credit card processing companies to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
> 
> **Security:**
> 
> This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.
> 
> **Links:**
> 
> This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we (Cybercartel International, Inc.) are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
> 
> Cybercartel International, Inc. - Copyright (c) 2004  
>
